let savollar11 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "abnormal",
      answer: "C. g'ayritabiiy",
      options: [
        "A. normal",
        "B. oddiy",
        "C. g'ayritabiiy",
        "D. noto'g'ri"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "bamboo",
      answer: "A. bambuk",
      options: [
        "A. bambuk",
        "B. qamish",
        "C. nay",
        "D. butazor"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "blossom",
      answer: "B. gul",
      options: [
        "A. kurtak",
        "B. gul",
        "C. barg",
        "D. shox"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "compass",
      answer: "D. kompas",
      options: [
        "A. xarita",
        "B. soat",
        "C. yo'nalish",
        "D. kompas"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "dialect",
      answer: "A. sheva",
      options: [
        "A. sheva",
        "B. til",
        "C. lahja",
        "D. nutq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "dishonest",
      answer: "C. vijdonsiz",
      options: [
        "A. noto'g'ri",
        "B. aldamchi",
        "C. vijdonsiz",
        "D. qallob"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "dwarf",
      answer: "B. gnom",
      options: [
        "A. pakana",
        "B. gnom",
        "C. gnom",
        "D. jo'ja"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "ecosystem",
      answer: "A. ekotizim",
      options: [
        "A. ekotizim",
        "B. tabiat",
        "C. muhit",
        "D. flora"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "fatal",
      answer: "D. halokatli",
      options: [
        "A. xavfli",
        "B. jiddiy",
        "C. halokat",
        "D. halokatli"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "impatient",
      answer: "B. besabr",
      options: [
        "A. shoshqaloq",
        "B. besabr",
        "C. bezovta",
        "D. asabiy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "leaf",
      answer: "C. barg",
      options: [
        "A. yaproq",
        "B. novda",
        "C. barg",
        "D. shox"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "manuscript",
      answer: "A. qo'lyozma",
      options: [
        "A. qo'lyozma",
        "B. hujjat",
        "C. kitob",
        "D. yozuv"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "marsh",
      answer: "B. botqoq",
      options: [
        "A. ko'l",
        "B. botqoq",
        "C. hovuz",
        "D. soy"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "patience",
      answer: "D. sabr",
      options: [
        "A. toqat",
        "B. bardosh",
        "C. chidam",
        "D. sabr"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "perfume",
      answer: "C. atir",
      options: [
        "A. hid",
        "B. yoqimli hid",
        "C. atir",
        "D. xushbo'y"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "pond",
      answer: "A. hovuz",
      options: [
        "A. hovuz",
        "B. ko'l",
        "C. ariq",
        "D. ko'lmak"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "proverb",
      answer: "B. maqol",
      options: [
        "A. hikmat",
        "B. maqol",
        "C. naql",
        "D. matal"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "pursuit",
      answer: "C. ta'qib",
      options: [
        "A. izlash",
        "B. ergashish",
        "C. ta'qib",
        "D. kuzatish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "to recite",
      answer: "A. bayon qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. bayon qilmoq",
        "B. o'qimoq",
        "C. gapirmoq",
        "D. kuylamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wilderness",
      answer: "D. yovvoyi tabiat",
      options: [
        "A. o'rmon",
        "B. cho'l",
        "C. dala",
        "D. yovvoyi tabiat"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar11;